If you lived here, you would be dead by now.
Toolbox Murders is a horror, mystery film directed by Tobe Hooper.
A historic Hollywood hotel houses a supernatural evil.
It's been subdued for decades, but when renovations
start, a series of murders take place.
Nell Barrows, played by Angela Bettis.
Steven Barrows, played by Brent Roam.
Chas Rooker, played by Rance Howard.
Julia Cunningham, played by Juliet Landau.
Luis Saucedo, played by Marco Rodríguez.
Ned Lundy, played by Adam Gierasch.
Toolbox Murders is a 2004 American slasher film directed by Tobe
Hooper, and written by Jace Anderson and Adam Gierasch.
It is a remake of the 1978 film The Toolbox Murders and was
produced by the same people behind the original.
The film is centered on the occupants of an apartment who
are stalked and murdered by a masked killer.
The film explores themes of psychopath, supernatural, gore, remake, murder.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.